As a small boat
Ocean
Sending big waves
Moving
Like how a single word can make an open heart
I could only have a game but I can make an explosion
And all these things I do not say Wrecking balls inside of my brain
I&#39;ll evening their cry Can you hear my voice this time
This is my fight song Take my song of life
Prove that I&#39;m the song
Lit my diet from now I&#39;ll be strong
I will play my fight song
And I do not really care if nobody else believes
Because I still have a lot of fight in me
Losing friends and I drive away sleep Everyone is worried about me
In too deep Let&#39;s say I&#39;m too deep (too deep)
And it&#39;s been two years I miss my house
But there&#39;s a fire in my bones and I still believe Yeah, I still believe
And all these things I do not say Wrecking balls inside of my brain
I&#39;ll evening their cry Can you hear my voice this time
This is my fight song Take my song of life
Prove that I&#39;m the song
Lit my diet from now I&#39;ll be strong
I will play my fight song
Et je ne me soucie pas vraiment si personne ne croit d'autre
Because I still have a lot of fight in me
A lot of fight in me
As a small boat
Ocean
Sending big waves
Moving
Like how a single word can make an open heart
I could only have one game
But I can make a blast
This is my fight song (Hey!) Take my song of life (Hey!)
Prove that I&#39;m the song (Hey!)
Lit my diet from now, I&#39;ll be strong (I&#39;ll be strong)
I will play my fight song
Et je ne me soucie pas vraiment si personne ne croit d'autre
Because I still have a lot of fight in me
Maintenant, je dois encore beaucoup de combat en moi